dgm-india.com 2018-04-03

# Privacy Policy

                                            Privacy Policy
                                              (Updated on May 28,
                                                       2014)
DGM India Internet Marketing Pvt Ltd ("we") are committed to protecting and respecting your
privacy.
This policy sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you
provide to us, will be processed by us. Please read the following carefully to understand our
policy and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it.
Information we may collect from you
Non-Personal Identifiable Information
We deliver advertisements across a multitude of Digital Content Provider properties. When you
visit one of these properties, our automated system may collect “click stream data” related to
your visit to the property. Click stream data is anonymous and can include information such as
your IP address, content or pages viewed, the date and time at which that content was viewed
and any interaction with content and advertisements on those properties. Technologies used to
collect this click stream data include cookies and Web beacons.
In order to improve performance, we augment our click stream data with non-personally-
identifiable behavioral and demographic data from Digital Content Providers and other partners.
This anonymous data may include such things as postal code, age and gender. It may also
include GPS location provided by Digital Content Providers with mobile properties.
Personally Identifiable Information
We collect personally identifiable information (email address) from you when you sign up for a
free newsletter or alerts with any of our website. While you can browse some sections of our site
without being a registered member, certain activities may require registration. We do use your
contact information to send you emails. You may always opt-out of receiving such information
from our respective products or sites. You may also provide us with personally identifiable
information (such as your name, email address, physical address or telephone number) when you
elect to contact us about this Privacy Policy or any other customer-service related matter. We
will only utilize such personal information for the purpose of responding to your query.
However, we do reserve the right to retain an archival record of all such correspondence.
We reserve the right to disclose personally identifiable information you have disclosed to us in
response to judicial process or court order or to provide information to law enforcement agencies
or in connection with an investigation of matters related to public safety, as permitted by law.
How We Use Collected Data
                                        DGM India Internet Marketing Pvt Ltd.
                          F90/34 2nd Floor, Okhla Industrial Area Phase 1, New Delhi 110020
                        t +91 (11) 46593888 f +91 (11) 46593895 e: info@dgm-india.com

We utilize the non-personal information described above to better customize the sort of
advertisements you see. We also aggregate anonymous cookie data in order to identify large
audience segments that assist advertisers in targeting their campaigns to the most relevant
Internet audience.
We may engage in email and direct mail marketing for some of our websites. Email may be an
integral part of the program, you sign up to receive email targeted to your interests at the time of
registration.
We may use click stream data as well as cookie data for non-targeting reasons such as frequency
capping, compliance, fraud prevention, billing, service fulfillment, ad reporting or delivery,
market research or product development purposes.
This information may also be combined with data from other sources, and shared with our
affiliates and partners for similar use.
Right to opt out
We respect your privacy considerations and hence this is an option, you may or may not provide
the data or information sought to be collected.
You can opt out of several similar programs and websites like us by visiting the Network
Advertising Initiative gateway opt-out site.
You may also adjust your computer’s web browser settings to refuse all cookies. However,
please note that because cookies are widely used, disabling the use of cookies in your web
browser may interfere with full use of various websites.
Personally identifiable information collected may be stored and processed in India or any other
country worldwide. You acknowledge and agree that personally identifiable information you
provide to us may be transferred outside of the country in which you reside. Providing such
information will constitute your consent to any such transfer.
Information Security
All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers. Where we have given you (or
where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our site, you are
responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with
anyone.
Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely
secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the
                                        DGM India Internet Marketing Pvt Ltd.
                          F90/34 2nd Floor, Okhla Industrial Area Phase 1, New Delhi 110020
                        t +91 (11) 46593888 f +91 (11) 46593895 e: info@dgm-india.com

security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have
received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent
unauthorised access.
CHILDREN UNDER 13 YEARS OF AGE
The website and the services provided by are not intended for persons under 13 years of age.
products and services are not developed or directed at children. We do not knowingly solicit
or collect any personally identifiable information including not from children under the age of
13, nor do we market our products or services to children under the age of 13
Transfer of Data Upon Change of Control
In the event that another company acquires all or substantially all of the assets of our business
through a consolidation, merger, asset purchase or other transaction, we reserve the right to
transfer all data (including any personally identifiable data) that is in our possession or under our
control to such acquiring party.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
We reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy by posting an updated version on
this page. The date on which the current Privacy Policy was posted will always be noted at the
top of this page. Any change we make to our Privacy Policy will be made in compliance with
applicable law.
Correspondence
If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence, including your email address.
This relates to your correspondence with us only – we do not gather users’ email addresses as
part of our online advertising business.
If you feel we are breaching any ethical Principles, please contact us at info@dgm-india.com or
mail to:
DGM India Internet Marketing Pvt. Ltd., F-90/34, 2nd Floor, Okhla Industrial Area, Phase 1,
New Delhi, Attn: Legal Department.
                                        DGM India Internet Marketing Pvt Ltd.
                          F90/34 2nd Floor, Okhla Industrial Area Phase 1, New Delhi 110020
                        t +91 (11) 46593888 f +91 (11) 46593895 e: info@dgm-india.com

Refund policy
You can pause your campaign and can claim for a refund with a 1 day notice over email. Once
the campaign is paused, the pending balance will be refunded after all outstanding/pending
charges are deducted.
How do I get a refund after pausing my campaign?
Payments made will be refunded by cheque/NEFT/RTGS within a maximum of 30 days from
date of pause request.
What are the cancellation/amendment charges?
There are no other cancellation or amendment charges where campaign has been ran and put on
hold, only the pending outstanding /pending charges are deducted from the available balance of
the merchant/advertiser. If NO campaign has been run by you and need refund of whole amount
2.5% of payment gateway charges will be deducted.
                                       DGM India Internet Marketing Pvt Ltd.
                         F90/34 2nd Floor, Okhla Industrial Area Phase 1, New Delhi 110020
                       t +91 (11) 46593888 f +91 (11) 46593895 e: info@dgm-india.com
